<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>politics by tedk42</title>
    <link>https://edify42.github.io/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content on politics by tedk42</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 13:41:44 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://edify42.github.io/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Climate Change Nuclear Investment</title>
      <link>https://edify42.github.io/politics/posts/climate-change-nuclear-investment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 13:41:44 +1100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edify42.github.io/politics/posts/climate-change-nuclear-investment/</guid>
      <description>Climate action is long overdue. Nuclear power investment is inevitable. The source of most energy on Earth was from our Sun at some point in time. Our Sun is one big nuclear fusion reactor.
I&amp;rsquo;ve talked and argued with many smart people about nuclear power. Some were scientists, others with acedemic credentials of some kind that had an opinion on the topic. I remember clearly struggling to argue with them. To a point where I really couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand why they were so anti-nuclear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Democracy Is Broken Here Is a Fix</title>
      <link>https://edify42.github.io/politics/posts/democracy-is-broken-here-is-a-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Sep 2021 23:30:59 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edify42.github.io/politics/posts/democracy-is-broken-here-is-a-fix/</guid>
      <description>What is this shit that&amp;rsquo;s called a government? Ok that&amp;rsquo;s a bit harsh - the roads, bridges, hospitals, police and doctors out there are because we have a working government.
I appreciate what democracy has done for our civilisation for the past 2000 years. But when does an old system become archaic and outdated? When has it served it&amp;rsquo;s purpose and is no longer fit for modern society?
I strongly believe democracy&amp;rsquo;s time is up and it&amp;rsquo;s time we elect our officials in a more thoughtful way and it all starts with WHO has a right to vote.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delta strain and Antilockdown realisations</title>
      <link>https://edify42.github.io/politics/posts/delta-strain-and-antilockdown-realisations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2021 12:03:25 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edify42.github.io/politics/posts/delta-strain-and-antilockdown-realisations/</guid>
      <description>We fucked it up. We let the delta variant get a strong hold on us as a population and it&amp;rsquo;s here to stay.
It wasn&amp;rsquo;t even 3 months ago, things were really looking up in the trans- oceanic area. There were talks of a travel bubble opening up, I even got to holiday with my partner in New Zealand in June. When we got back though, we faced a long lockdown which we&amp;rsquo;re still in today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Is Antigovernment</title>
      <link>https://edify42.github.io/politics/posts/crypto-is-antigovernment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 14:18:27 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edify42.github.io/politics/posts/crypto-is-antigovernment/</guid>
      <description>Cryptocurrencies are bad for the environment. It&amp;rsquo;s an incredibly ineffecient way of processing transactions. It&amp;rsquo;s a bit like burning a forest as a way of keeping your neighbourhood warm. I say these when looking at the more popular cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum but to a degree, they apply to all of them.
Crypto also offers an avenue of transactions which are absent of any governing or financial regulatory systems. They rely on distributed parties agreeing whether transactions should proceed or not as opposed to a singular body which can authoritatively approve or deny a transaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://edify42.github.io/politics/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 13:23:18 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edify42.github.io/politics/about/</guid>
      <description>Born late 80s in Australia.
Grew up in Western Suburbs Sydney.
Married, maybe with kids soon. Has 1 dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Property is a ponzi scheme</title>
      <link>https://edify42.github.io/politics/posts/housing-affordability/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 11:52:59 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://edify42.github.io/politics/posts/housing-affordability/</guid>
      <description>It wasn&amp;rsquo;t always like this, at least not for as long as I remember. I&amp;rsquo;m watching this great catastrophe happen in front of me and I can&amp;rsquo;t help but feel helpless.
Let&amp;rsquo;s first rewind to when being a &amp;lsquo;millionaire&amp;rsquo; was something to aspire to. Having a million dollars meant you could do nearly anything you want. My memories of this feeling was in the late 90s and probably crept into the early 2000s.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
